Guide to the Paul Kwilecki photographs and papers, circa 1910-2008, bulk 1960-2008 RL.00790
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Shade Tobacco, 1962-1982 and undated; 2 folders 21 prints
  - Three workers resting on benches under shade, 1965 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    Workers resting in field. They are in the process of stringing the plants up.
  - Woman hoeing tobacco plants, 1965 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    Woman hoeing tender new plants. Note the layers of clothes she is wearing.
  - Workers resting under shades, 1965 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Man with cigarette picking leaves, 1966 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    Worker picking leaves. Lowest leaves are picked first. Leaves are stacked on a wagon and hauled to barn to cure.
  - Two women (head shot) in front of tobacco barn, 1966 (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    Two women resting outside barn.
  - Men shooting craps in the field while they wait for the wagon to return, W.B. Miller and Son farm (1), 1966 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Men shooting craps in the field while they wait for the wagon to return, W.B. Miller and Son farm (2), 1966 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Shade tobacco workers shooting craps (Box PHO 8, Print [3])
  - Stringer inside barn, 1968 (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Three children on floor of tobacco barn, 1968 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    These are children of the women working just out of camera range, stringing tobacco inside the cool, cathedral-like barns. They play all day on the dirt floor. Their mothers are stringing leaves which will be hung in the barn ceiling to cure.
  - Woman sewing shades, 1968 (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Willie James Igler, tobacco worker, 1968 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    He was a worker and foreman. This picture was taken at his home. He had eleven children and several grandchildren.
  - Two boys hiding in tobacco leaves, 1971 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    These children do not pick leaves despite their having boards in their hands. They are playing under the ripe, aromatic plants. Their jobs were to do odds and ends.
  - In the wake of shade tobacco, 1982 Oct. (Box PHO 8, Print 94-1082-5)
  - In the wake of shade tobacco, 1982 Sept. (Box PHO 8, Print 86-982-22)
  - Tobacco hand's house, 1982 Aug. (Box PHO 8, Print 20-882-23a)
    Tobacco hand's house long after tobacco had ceased to be grown in Decatur County. Such places by 1980 were the worst of slums.
  - Man standing on front porch, 1982 Sept. (Box PHO 8, Print 87-982-11)
  - W.B. Miller and Sons Farm, Decatur County, 1968 (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - Color snapshots related to Shade Tobacco project, circa 1961; 17 photographs (Box PHO 29)
- Shoppers, 1977-1982; 2 folders 23 prints
  [See also Oversize Box 2.]
  - Blind man being assisted in his grocery buying by friend, 1980 Apr. (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print 38-480-2)
  - Preparing to enter the Bargain Center, 1978 July (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print 49-778-25)
  - At checkout, 1980 Mar. (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print 26-380-9a)
  - At Elmore's department store, 1981 Aug. (Box PHO 8, Print 99-881-16a)
  - Waiting at checkout, 1980 Mar. (Box PHO 8, Print 24-380-3)
  - Claustrophobic grocery store, 1982 Mar. (Box PHO 8, Print 18-382-13a)
  - Second print of At checkout, above, 1980 Mar. (Box PHO 8, Print 26-380-9a)
  - Visiting, 1978 Sept. (Box PHO 8, Print 75-978-15)
  - Typical shopper, 1980 Mar. (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print 28-380-19)
    Typical shopper with forlorn, absent-minded look on her face, which you see everywhere when shoppers are preoccupied.
  - Woman putting bacon in grocery cart, 1980 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
  - Gossip, Wynn-Dixie Grocery, 1981 Aug. (Box PHO 8, Print 101-881-21a)
  - Women waiting in line at grocery store for checkout, 1980 Feb. (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print 19-280-3)
  - Shoppers, 1981 Jan. (Box PHO 8, Print 16-181-2)
    People don't realize how they look when they're preoccupied with shopping. I set about to photograph their expressions which are those of a stalker.
  - What an expression! 1981 Dec. (Box PHO 8, Print 145-1281-3a)
  - Woman crossing Broad Street, 1979 June (Box PHO 8, Print 94-679-15)
    Note the fan she carries with her.
  - Grocery buying, 1980 Mar. (Box PHO 8, Print 28-380-18)
  - Women talking in grocery store, 1977 Aug. (Oversize-box 2, Print 96-877-15a)
  - Women loading groceries in their car, 1977 April (Oversize-box 2, Print 16-477-11)
    Typical supermarket entrance.
  - No known title, 1981 April (Box PHO 28, Print 48-481-10)
  - No known title, 1977 October (Box PHO 28, Print 107-1077-20A)
  - No known title, 1971 May 9 (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, 1981 April (Box PHO 28, Print 49-481-1)
  - No known title, 1981 April (Box PHO 28, Print 49-481-10)
- Swine Time, 1974-1980; 1 folders 6 prints
  - Swine Time. Climax, Ga., 1980 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 9, Print 106-1180-19)
  - Two politicians and a preacher. Which is which? 1980 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 9, Print 118-1180-25a)
  - Junk table with women, 1975 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 9, Print unnumbered)
  - Houses, tents and umbrellas, 1975 (Box PHO 9, Print unnumbered)
    People listening to and watching the hog calling contest.
  - A table of secondhand wares for sale. Typical junk, 1979 Nov. (Box PHO 9, Print 151-1179-3a)
  - Husband and wife, 1974 (Oversize-box 2, Print unnumbered)
- Social Events, 1976 September; 1 folders 2 prints
  - Wedding reception at the bride's home, 1976 Sept. (Box PHO 8, Print 117-976-9)
  - Woman with plate at reception, 1976 Sept. (Box PHO 8, Print (117-976?))
    A wedding reception for Chris Dollar.
- Willis Park, 1969-2001; 2 folders 63 prints
  - Woman taking a picture of her son's company posed in front of the Confederate monument, 1989 May (Box PHO 10, Print 28-589-12)
    The occasion was the dedication of a memorial to Vietnam veterans.
  - Man in phone booth, 1976 July (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 776-14)
  - Men at Armistice Day ceremony, 1979 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 156-1179-15a)
  - 1978 Sept. (Box PHO 10, Print 71-978-6a)
    Before the park was redone people sat and watched and waited. Now the benches are gone and people only pass through the park.
  - Bike fest, 1999 June (Box PHO 10, Print 9-699-29)
  - Mike Gast testing mike for spring festival, 1977 May (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 27-577-4a)
  - Bainbridge High School Band playing for some ceremony, 1976 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 135-1176-9a)
  - Another view of the park, 1980 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 38-480-32)
  - Gospel singers in the gazebo on a Saturday afternoon, 1979 June (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 86-679)
  - Willis Park United Daughters of the Confederacy posing under the statue on Confederate Memorial Day, 1974 (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print unnumbered)
    A newspaper photographer was taking their picture.
  - Little girl wetting her pants (1), 1979 June (Box PHO 10, Print 76-679-27)
    This set shows a little girl (1) about to wet her pants, (2) wetting them under the watchful eye of the other children, and (3) she continues looking at the fish in the pool as though nothing had happened while the black children look to me for some reaction.
  - Little girl wetting her pants (2), 1979 June (Box PHO 10, Print 76-679-29)
  - Little girl wetting her pants (3), 1979 June (Box PHO 10, Print 76-679-30)
  - Before the park was redone, 1980 Apr. (Understandings) (Box PHO 10, Print 42-480-25)
  - The Confederate statue in early morning fog, 1986 Feb. (Box PHO 10, Print 8-286)
  - British rowing team for 1996 Olympics, 1994 July (Box PHO 10, Print 19-794-29)
  - Two veterans in front of gazebo, 1996 Nov. (Box PHO 10, Print 42-1196-26)
  - Wedding reception, Willis Park, 1989 Sept. (Box PHO 10, Print 43-989-25a)
  - Armistice Day, Willis Park, 1969 (Box PHO 10, Print 18 W.P. 3)
  - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 29-498-15a)
  - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 30-498-28a)
  - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 30-498-17a)
  - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 30-498-14a)
  - [Veteran in the park], 2000 (Box PHO 10, Print 10-9-2000-19)
  - [Bainbridge High School Reunion], 2000 (Box PHO 10, Print 13-9-2000-19)
  - Santa in Willis Park, 2001 Dec. (Box PHO 10, Print 27-1201-26)
  - Children ready to march to the gazebo for wedding, Willis Park, 2001 (Box PHO 10, Print 22-11-01)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 4-595-10)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 3-595-16)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 3-595-20)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-597-30)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-599-6)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-597-8)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-597-23)
  - Couples posed on war memorial, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 39-598-27)
    Couples unwittingly posed by snapshooting mothers against the memorial to Decatur County men who have died in all wars since the Civil War.
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 38-598-16)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May (Box PHO 10, Print 6-599-24)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 38-598-31)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1990 May (Box PHO 10, Print 7-590-18(8))
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1996 May (Box PHO 10, Print 12-596-12)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 4-595-23)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 36-598-26)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-599-14)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 4-595-13)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1994 May (Box PHO 10, Print 13-594-29)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May (Box PHO 10, Print 10-597-7)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May (Box PHO 10, Print 7-599-30)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1996 May (Box PHO 10, Print 12-596-18)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May (Box PHO 10, Print 3-595-21)
  - Spectator, Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May (Box PHO 10, Print 8-599-28)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 38-598-13)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 39-598-13)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May (Box PHO 10, Print 40-598-18)
  - [Spectators, Junior-Senior Prom], 2000 (Box PHO 10, Print 8-5-00-10a)
    They are not applauding but fighting southern Georgia gnats.
  - A girl and her date, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 3-4-01)
  - Promenade begins, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 3-4-01-24A)
  - Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 4-4-01)
  - Spectators, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr. (Box PHO 10, Print 4-4-01-27)
  - No known title, 1995 May (Box PHO 28, Print 4-595-16)
- Religion, 1965-2000; 8 folders 110 prints
  - 1985 Feb. (Box PHO 6, Print 6-285-8)
    This is typical of the change from old to new church buildings by small congregations out in the sparsely populated county. Unfortunately in most cases the new structures don't measure up to the old. Instead of wood they use concrete block. Instead of blending into the landscape, they are a caustic white and stand out.
  - Iron City Church and country road, 1985 Mar. (Box PHO 6, Print 8-385-12)
  - Mt. Zion A.B. Church, 1979 Mar. (Box PHO 6, Print 34-379-1)
    Note the dog asleep at left next to the church.
  - Mt. Zion A.M.E. Church, circa 1970 (Box PHO 6, Print unnumbered)
  - Advent Christian Church, 1985 May (Box PHO 6, Print 17-585-8)
    This church raises barrenness and impersonality to an art, even to symmetry. The screen doors divide the façade in half: one air conditioner per side; one untrimmed boxwood per side. The name squarely in the center.
  - St. Paul's Missionary Baptist Church with Christmas wreaths on doors, 1980 Dec. (Box PHO 6, Print 123-1280-4)
  - The First Baptist Church of Bainbridge, 1982 May (Box PHO 6, Print 51-582-1)
    It sits like a fortress flanked by a parking lot filled with the latest model cars. This picture tells more than many Baptists would want to hear.
  - Doorway, Mt. Zion A.M.E. Church, 1989 Jan. (Box PHO 6, Print 9-189)
    Older churches frequently had two doors, one for each aisle. This church, which meets only one Sunday a month, is set back behind tall pines, obscured from the road. The idea of the sign is a conceit. Who will see it?
  - Antioch Primitive Baptist Church, circa 1978 (Box PHO 6, Print unnumbered)
    The church steeple will soon be extinct on small churches such as this. In fact since this picture was made this minor gesture to steeples has been removed and nothing put in its place.
  - An anonymous church, like so many other new churches, 1985 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 12-485)
    Note the steeple, the merest nod to convention, a wooden box set over an open space (with nothing to support it). Still, the sunlight is beautiful on it.
  - Jeanette Rogers seated on the pulpit of her church, 1993 Mar. (Box PHO 6, Print 2-393-25)
  - Pastor Jeanette Rogers and daughter Ginger Jean at their front door, Mitchell County, 1993 Oct. (Box PHO 6, Print 4-1093-10)
  - Before baptism, Mt. Zion Church, Cyrene, Ga., 1981 July (Box PHO 6, Print 93-781-10)
  - Footwashing, Holiness Temple #11, Camilla, Ga., 1983 (Box PHO 6, Print 69-1183?)
  - Minister just prior to baptizing, First A.B. Church of Camilla, Ga., 1983 Aug. (Box PHO 6, Print 45-883-20a)
  - Minister hugging woman who has just come out of an ecstatic experience, 1983 Nov. (Box PHO 6, Print 69-1183-15)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, Pelham, Ga., 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 6, Print 14-384-25)
    They had just finished building their new church with their own hands and this was the dedication. These are the most truly integrated congregations I've ever seen. Black and white work and worship side by side.
  - 1983 Aug. (Box PHO 6, Print 44-883-8a)
    Music was furnished by piano, guitar, and drums. The woman in the hat has gotten so carried away she's dancing. Note the similarity of gesture to some very ancient Jewish dances.
  - 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 6, Print 3-84-16)
    The woman, right, is the minister. The man praying and holding her hand is a deacon who has just finished serving 15 years for murder. This was an extremely long and emotional service.
  - Healing Temple. Sunday School, 1983 Aug. (Box PHO 6, Print 44-883-21a)
  - 1984 Jan. (Box PHO 6, Print 3-184-33)
    A three hour service at this church on Sunday morning is not unusual. Music plays a major role. Before it's over, people are dancing in the aisles and experiencing ecstasy.
  - 1984 Jan. (Box PHO 6, Print 2-184-18)
    This is part of the same service as shown in the previous picture.
  - 1983 Aug. (Box PHO 6, Print 44-883-220)
    The proximity of sex to religion was blatant in this service. The minister is saying that 'it's coming,' meaning the spirit. He says he can't hold it back. Shortly he begins to jerk and shake, replicating orgasm.
  - Indoor baptism, First A.B. Church, Camilla, Ga., 1983 Aug. (Box PHO 6, Print 45-883-30a)
  - Baptism on the last night of revival at Mt. Zuma, 1991 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 8-491-24)
  - Baptismal pool, Mt. Zuma, 1991 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 8-491-5)
  - Baptism at Mt. Zuma, 1991 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 8-491-19)
  - First baptism in Mt. Zuma's new pool behind the church, 1982 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 38-482-27a)
    Formerly, they baptized in the Flint River. Rev. Mitchell seen at left.
  - Interior, First African Baptist Church, Bainbridge, 1980 Nov. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 111-1180-3)
  - Sunday school on steps of Pilgrim Rest A.M.E. Church. Decatur County, 1980 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 102-1080-8)
  - Mt. Zuma baptizing in the Flint River, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 19-477-13)
    Rev. Mitchell, left. Lisa Spear, lower right. Ben Edwards, extreme right. See photo of Lisa Spear's grave.
  - Mt. Zuma baptizing in the Flint River, 1977 Apr. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 20-477-14a)
  - Mt. Horum Church, 1980 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 97-1080-3)
    See other photographs of exterior and interior before and after abandonment.
  - Interior of Antioch Baptist Church on Lake Douglas Road, 1975 (Box PHO 6, Print unnumbered)
  - Privy behind Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Decatur County, 1989 Nov. (Box PHO 6, Print 55-1189-7)
  - Rev. Jeffrey baptizing at Mt. Zion. Decatur County, 1981 July (Box PHO 6, Print 94-781-28)
  - Second print of privy behind Moses Chapel, above, 1989 Nov. (Box PHO 6, Print 55-1189-6)
  - Window in First Presbyterian Church, Bainbridge, seen from outside, 1979 Jan. (Box PHO 6, Print 13-179)
  - Consecration service prior to Sunday morning service. St. Mary's, near Baconton, Mitchell Co., Ga., 1984 Feb. (Box PHO 6, Print 11-284-33)
  - Pilgrim Rest A.M.E.Church. Old structure and new building, 1985 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 16-485-10)
    The old structure has been torn down.
  - Rev. Jeffry in the living room of his home, West Bainbridge, Ga., 1982 Sept. (Box PHO 6, Print 89-982-5)
  - First baptism in Mt. Zuma pool, 1982 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 38-482-24a)
  - Rev. Lois Hurst with congregants, Mitchell Co., 1984 July (Box PHO 6, Print 42-784)
  - Rev. Mitchell baptizing at last night of revival, Mt. Zuma, 1991 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 8-491-23)
  - Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church revival, group of two photographs:
    - Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1977 May (Box PHO 6, Print 1: 29-577-16)
      This is a set of pictures made at a revival. Supper was served first, then singing and guitar playing. Then preaching. Note the faces.
    - Gospel singers at Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1977 May (Box PHO 6, Print 2: 29-577-20a)
  - Window in First Baptist Church, Bainbridge (5 x 7), circa 1968 (Box PHO 6, Print unnumbered)
  - New Hope Missionary Baptist Church, West Bainbridge, Ga., 1982 Apr. (Box PHO 6, Print 43-482-17a)
  - Entrance to Mt. Zion Missionary Baptist Church, Cyrene, Ga., 1980 Feb., ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 11-280-2)
  - Privy and pew in church yard. St. Luke, Faceville, Ga., 1980 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 6, Print 97-1080-7)
  - Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Ga., 1980 Feb. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 7, Print 16-280-4)
  - Baptism pool in front yard of the Attapulgus African Baptist Church, 1980 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 7, Print 105-1080-6)
  - Union Springs Primitive Baptist Church. Miller County, Ga., 1980 Nov. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 7, Print 117-1180-7)
  - Rev. Lois Hurst, Assembly of God, Meigs, Ga., 1984 June (Box PHO 7, Print 40-684-9)
  - Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Ga., 1982 Mar. (Box PHO 7, Print 26-382-3)
    This is a beautiful old church in a stereotypical southern setting. However, it was moved to its present location about thirty years ago from an area that was being inundated by Jim Woodruf Dam. It is no longer in use.
  - Nearing the end of the foot washing service, 1983 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 69-1183-16a)
    This is an emotional ceremony and the woman dancing is having an ecstatic experience.
  - Moses Chapel seen from the rear, near Recovery, Ga., 1989 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 54-1189-17)
  - Mt. Horum, northeast of Climax, Ga., 1983 Dec. (Box PHO 7, Print 1: 75-1283)
    This is the first image in a group of six that tells the story of Mt. Horum. Once a relatively active congregation, it declined until finally one Sunday the worshipers left and never came back. The altar, pews, even the prayer books remain, but the grounds are grown up in weeds and saplings.
  - Mt. Horum interior, 1978 Dec. (Box PHO 7, Print 2: 124-1278-12a)
  - Mt. Horum interior, 1978 Dec. (Box PHO 7, Print 3: 124-1278-7a)
  - Mt. Horum, 1989 May (Box PHO 7, Print 4: 27-589-20)
    In this shot the vine indicates the disuse the church has fallen into. Also note the chain on the door is the same throughout all the picture.
  - Mt. Horum, 1991 May (Box PHO 7, Print 5: 10-591-15)
    This is a recent interior shot showing how the church was left. I did not touch or arrange anything. However, I was extremely cautious getting in through a window. The largest diamondback rattlesnake I ever saw was killed less than a mile from this location.
  - Mt. Horum, 1991 Mar. (Box PHO 7, Print 6: 5-391-22)
    The final shot in the series. Compare this to the first picture. The building is askew, but little else is different.
  - Covered dish supper after revival, 1977 May (Box PHO 7, Print 30-577-8a)
  - Tent revival, 1981 Sept. (Box PHO 7, Print 117-981-13)
  - The wedding of Brenda Mitchell, 1983 Sept. (Box PHO 7, Print 46-983-28)
    Rev. Mitchell is an attendant; his brother, a minister from Thomasville, officiated.
  - Interior of Sunday School, Pilgrim Rest A.M.E. Church just off West River Road, 1980 Oct. (Box PHO 7, Print 102-1080-10)
  - Wedding ceremony, mother of the groom, 1983 Sept. (Box PHO 7, Print 47-983-17)
  - Sunday School of God's Tabernacle just off Lake Douglas Road, 1986 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 22-1186-9)
  - Sunday school class and minister on steps, Mt. Zion A.M.E. Church, 1981 Aug. (Box PHO 7, Print 106-881-3)
    See my notes for a fuller description of this photo.
  - God's Tabernacle, 1986 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 23-1186-5)
    Back row: the minister and assistant minister. The man in front is serving his apprenticeship. They are strong, dedicated individuals.
  - Brenda Mitchell, her husband, and Reginald, their son, in their mobile home, 1985 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 50-1185-12)
    I photographed their wedding (she is Rev. Mitchell's daughter) a couple of years before. The husband works as a mechanic for Kmart but wants to be a preacher like his father-in-law.
  - Bishop, Church of God in Christ, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 44-1197-27)
  - Minister and Sunday School class cleaning out baptismal pool (PZ will look up name of church later - remind him), 1997 July (Box PHO 7, Print 17-797-9a)
  - Boy and girl behind New Abundant Life sign (remind PZ - look up name of church), 1997 Aug. (Box PHO 7, Print 19-897-24)
  - New minister at Nelson Chapel AME Church, 1997 Aug. (Box PHO 7, Print 23-897-14)
  - Minister in white with crosses (remind PZ - look up name of church), 1997 Aug. (Box PHO 7, Print 19-897-12)
  - Minister, Church of God in Christ, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 44-1197-6a)
  - Store front church, 1986 Oct. (Box PHO 7, Print 19-1086-3)
  - Interior, Sunday morning, Fellowship of Faith church, 1997 Aug. (Box PHO 7, Print 20-897-17a)
  - Interior of Church of God in Christ, women singing, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 7, Print 45-1197-23)
  - Night exterior of Fellowship of Faith church, 1997 Feb. (Box PHO 7, Print 5-297-17a)
  - Night shot of St. Luke Free Will Baptist Church, 1997 Feb. (Box PHO 7, Print 6-297-10)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church (formerly a filling station), 1997 June (Box PHO 7, Print 14-697-33)
  - Easter Sunday, First Methodist Church, 1995 Apr. (Box PHO 7, Print 1-495-32)
  - Minister, Fellowship of Faith Curch, 1994 May (Box PHO 7, Print 14-594-5)
  - Easter Sunday, First Methodist Church, 1995 Apr. (Box PHO 7, Print 2-495-10)
  - Street preacher, Beecher Thomas, with New Testament in his pocket, 1994 Mar. (Box PHO 7, Print 7-394-15)
  - Sunday School teacher outside First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May (Box PHO 7, Print 12-594-17)
  - Sunday School student on steps, First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May (Box PHO 7, Print 12-594-28)
  - Couple standing in front of First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May (Box PHO 7, Print 12-594-22)
  - Man and woman ascending steps of First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May (Box PHO 7, Print 12-594-25)
  - Woman on steps of First Methodist Church, Bainbridge, 1994 Apr. (Box PHO 7, Print 8-494-25)
  - Church front, Brinson, Ga., 1996 Feb. (Box PHO 7, Print 6-296-18)